<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Movies on REG Blog</title>
    <link>https://regblog.github.io/categories/movies/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Movies on REG Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 10:57:40 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://regblog.github.io/categories/movies/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Dev Patel&#39;s &#39;Monkey Man&#39;: A Tale of Vengeance and Divinity</title>
      <link>https://regblog.github.io/movies/dev-patel-monkey-man/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 10:57:40 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://regblog.github.io/movies/dev-patel-monkey-man/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Directed by: Dev Patel&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Starring: Dev Patel, Sharlto Copley, Pitobash, Vipin Sharma, Sikandar Kher, Adithi Kalkunte, Sobhita Dhulipala, Ashwini Kalsekar, Makrand Deshpande, Jatin Malik, Zakir Hussain&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Written by: Dev Patel, Paul Angunawela, John Collee&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Produced by: Dev Patel, Jomon Thomas, Jordan Peele, Win Rosenfeld, Ian Cooper, Basil Iwanyk, Erica Lee, Christine Haebler, Anjay Nagpal&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Rating: ★★★★☆&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In &amp;ldquo;Monkey Man,&amp;rdquo; Dev Patel takes us on a thrilling journey through the streets of Mumbai. The film showcases Patel&amp;rsquo;s prowess as a director and actor and delves deep into the symbolic realms of religion and mythology, particularly focusing on the deity Hanuman.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Late Night With The Devil: A Sinister Journey Back to 1977</title>
      <link>https://regblog.github.io/movies/late-night-with-the-devil/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 23:59:54 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://regblog.github.io/movies/late-night-with-the-devil/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directed by:&lt;/strong&gt; Colin Cairnes, Cameron Cairnes&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Starring:&lt;/strong&gt; David Dastmalchian, Laura Gordon, Ian Bliss, Fayssal Bazzi, Ingrid Torelli, Rhys Auteri, Georgina Haig, Josh Quong Tart&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Written by:&lt;/strong&gt; Colin Cairnes, Cameron Cairnes&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Produced by:&lt;/strong&gt; Mat Govoni, Adam White, John Molloy, Roy Lee, Steven Schneider, Derek Dauchy&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;rating-&#34;&gt;Rating: ★★★★★&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Late Night With The Devil&amp;rdquo; is a masterful horror film that takes viewers on a terrifying journey back to the late 1970s. Directed by the talented duo Colin and Cameron Cairnes, and starring an ensemble cast led by David Dastmalchian and Laura Gordon, this movie has earned a resounding 5-star rating from me.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Mind-Bending World of Christopher Nolan&#39;s &#39;Memento&#39;</title>
      <link>https://regblog.github.io/movies/christopher-nolan-memento/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 13:45:14 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://regblog.github.io/movies/christopher-nolan-memento/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Christopher Nolan&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Memento&amp;rdquo; is a film that defies traditional storytelling, leaving its audience captivated and bewildered. Released in 2000, this neo-noir psychological thriller has become a hallmark of innovative filmmaking, employing a unique narrative structure that challenges the viewer&amp;rsquo;s perception of time and memory.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-heart-of-memento-leonard-shelbys-quest-for-justice&#34;&gt;The Heart of &amp;ldquo;Memento&amp;rdquo;: Leonard Shelby&amp;rsquo;s Quest for Justice&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At the heart of &amp;ldquo;Memento&amp;rdquo; is the character of Leonard Shelby, portrayed with compelling intensity by Guy Pearce. Leonard is a man trapped in a perpetual present, unable to form new memories due to anterograde amnesia. This condition, a result of a traumatic incident that also led to his wife&amp;rsquo;s murder, leaves Leonard in a constant state of confusion and vulnerability. Despite these challenges, he is driven by an unwavering determination to seek justice for his wife&amp;rsquo;s death.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dune: Part Two (2024) - A Breathtaking Continuation of the Epic Saga</title>
      <link>https://regblog.github.io/movies/dune-part-two/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 12:04:28 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://regblog.github.io/movies/dune-part-two/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directed by:&lt;/strong&gt; Denis Villeneuve&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Starring:&lt;/strong&gt; Timothée Chalamet, Zendaya, Rebecca Ferguson, Stellan Skarsgård, Cristopher Walken, Florence Pugh, Austin Butler, Javier Bardem, Josh Brolin, Dave Bautista, and others&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;rating-&#34;&gt;Rating: ★★★★★&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Dune: Part Two&amp;rdquo; is a masterful continuation of Denis Villeneuve&amp;rsquo;s adaptation of Frank Herbert&amp;rsquo;s classic science fiction novel. This sequel not only lives up to the expectations set by its predecessor but also elevates the story to new heights in terms of narrative depth and visual spectacle.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Boys in the Boat: Movie Day Tuesday</title>
      <link>https://regblog.github.io/movies/the-boys-in-the-boat-movie-day-tuesday/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 23:57:17 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://regblog.github.io/movies/the-boys-in-the-boat-movie-day-tuesday/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In an age defined by individual achievement and personal glory, &amp;ldquo;The Boys in the Boat&amp;rdquo; emerges as a beacon of collective endeavor and shared triumph. Set against the grim backdrop of the 1930s, a period marred by the Great Depression and the ominous rise of Nazi Germany, this remarkable story unfolds. Daniel James Brown&amp;rsquo;s narrative masterfully captures the essence of an era and the indomitable spirit of a group of young men from the University of Washington.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Shift - A Cinematic Journey Through the Trials of Job</title>
      <link>https://regblog.github.io/movies/the-shift/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 00:04:59 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://regblog.github.io/movies/the-shift/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the ever-evolving landscape of cinema, it&amp;rsquo;s rare to find a film that daringly intertwines spirituality, science fiction, and profound human struggles. &amp;ldquo;The Shift,&amp;rdquo; directed and written by Brock Heasley, is a unique addition to the 2023 film roster, offering a modern-day reflection of the timeless tale of Job from the Bible. In this post, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore how &amp;ldquo;The Shift&amp;rdquo; reimagines the Book of Job&amp;rsquo;s themes within a sci-fi setting, the challenges it presents, and the deeper meanings it conveys.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
