<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Food on REG Blog</title>
    <link>https://regblog.github.io/categories/food/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Food on REG Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 23:42:10 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://regblog.github.io/categories/food/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Festive Cranberry Pecan Goat Cheese Log: A Holiday Appetizer Delight</title>
      <link>https://regblog.github.io/food/pecan-cranberry-goat-cheese-log/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 23:42:10 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://regblog.github.io/food/pecan-cranberry-goat-cheese-log/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The holiday season is a time for warmth, cheer, and, most importantly, delicious food! If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for an easy yet elegant appetizer to grace your Christmas or New Year&amp;rsquo;s table, look no further than this Cranberry Pecan Goat Cheese Log. Infused with the rich flavors of mature cheddar, fresh herbs, and sweet cranberries, this dish is a delightful blend of textures and tastes to impress your guests.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;ingredients&#34;&gt;Ingredients&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;½ cup dried cranberries&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;1 teaspoon butter (salted)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;½ cup finely chopped pecans&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;¼ teaspoon kosher salt&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;8 oz goat cheese, softened&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;3 oz Mature/Sharp Cheddar Cheese, grated&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;2 tablespoons fresh parsley, finely chopped&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;2 teaspoons fresh rosemary, finely chopped&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Honey for drizzling&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;instructions&#34;&gt;Instructions&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;preparing-the-cranberries&#34;&gt;Preparing the Cranberries&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Boil Water&lt;/strong&gt;: In a microwave-safe bowl or on the stovetop, bring half a cup of water to a rolling boil.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Soak the Cranberries&lt;/strong&gt;: Add the dried cranberries to the boiling water. Let them sit and soften for about 2 minutes. This process rehydrates the cranberries, enhancing their flavor and texture.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Drain and Cool&lt;/strong&gt;: Carefully drain the cranberries. Set them aside to cool down. This step is crucial as adding hot cranberries to the cheese mixture would affect its consistency.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;toasting-the-pecans&#34;&gt;Toasting the Pecans&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Melt Butter&lt;/strong&gt;: Heat a small sauté pan over medium-low heat. Add a teaspoon of butter and let it melt, coating the pan.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Toast the Pecans&lt;/strong&gt;: Add the finely chopped pecans to the pan. Sprinkle in the kosher salt. This will enhance the nutty flavor of the pecans.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stir Constantly&lt;/strong&gt;: Increase the heat slightly. Continuously stir the pecans for 2-3 minutes. Watch for a golden color and a fragrant aroma, signs they&amp;rsquo;re toasted perfectly.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cooling the Pecans&lt;/strong&gt;: Remove from heat and transfer the pecans to a medium-sized bowl. Let them cool to room temperature. This prevents the pecans from melting the goat cheese when mixed.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;making-the-cheese-mixture&#34;&gt;Making the Cheese Mixture&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chop Cranberries&lt;/strong&gt;: Once cooled, transfer the cranberries to a cutting board. Chop them into medium-fine pieces. This ensures an even distribution of cranberry flavor in every bite.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Combine with Herbs and Pecans&lt;/strong&gt;: Add the chopped cranberries, freshly chopped parsley, and rosemary to the bowl with the cooled pecans. Stir well to combine.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cream the Goat Cheese&lt;/strong&gt;: Place the softened goat cheese in a separate medium-sized bowl. Stir it with a spoon or spatula until it&amp;rsquo;s creamy and smooth.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Add Pecan Mixture and Cheddar&lt;/strong&gt;: Mix the pecan-cranberry-herb mixture in half along with the grated mature cheddar cheese. Stir until all components are evenly incorporated into the goat cheese.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;shaping-and-coating-the-cheese-log&#34;&gt;Shaping and Coating the Cheese Log&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Prepare the Surface&lt;/strong&gt;: Lay a large plastic wrap (about 14-16 inches long) on a clean work surface.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From the Log&lt;/strong&gt;: Place the goat cheese mixture in the center of the plastic wrap. Using the wrap as an aid, mold the mixture into a log shape, similar to the original form of the goat cheese.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chill the Log&lt;/strong&gt;: Place the wrapped cheese log in the refrigerator for 30-40 minutes. Alternatively, for quicker setting, freeze it for about 10 minutes.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Prepare for Coating&lt;/strong&gt;: Spread another sheet of plastic wrap or parchment paper on your work surface. Distribute the remaining pecan mixture evenly on it.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Coat the Log&lt;/strong&gt;: Unwrap the chilled cheese log. Roll it over the pecan mixture, pressing slightly so the nuts and herbs adhere to the surface. Ensure the entire log, including the ends, is well-coated.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reshape if Needed&lt;/strong&gt;: If the log loses its shape during coating, gently mold it back into form. Wrap it again and refrigerate if not serving immediately.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;serving-the-cheese-log&#34;&gt;Serving the Cheese Log&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Room Temperature Before Serving&lt;/strong&gt;: Remove the cheese log from the refrigerator about 15-20 minutes before serving. This allows the cheese to soften slightly, enhancing its flavor and texture.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Drizzle with Honey&lt;/strong&gt;: Drizzle the log right before serving for a touch of sweetness.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Garnish and Serve&lt;/strong&gt;: Optionally, sprinkle additional fresh herbs over the log for a fresh, aromatic touch. Serve the cheese log with an assortment of crackers, crostini, or celery sticks for a delightful appetizer.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;conclusion&#34;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This Cranberry Pecan Goat Cheese Log is not just an appetizer; it&amp;rsquo;s a celebration of holiday flavors and textures. Whether hosting a grand feast or a cozy gathering, this easy-to-make dish will surely be the star of your holiday spread. Enjoy the harmonious blend of sweet, savory, and creamy in every bite, and watch as it becomes a new festive favorite!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Easy Homemade Grilled Tandoori Chicken Recipe - Flavorful &amp; Quick!</title>
      <link>https://regblog.github.io/food/tandoori-chicken/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 23:44:07 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://regblog.github.io/food/tandoori-chicken/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to a culinary adventure where simplicity meets extraordinary flavor! Today&amp;rsquo;s blog post reveals an incredibly easy-to-follow Grilled Tandoori Chicken recipe perfect for any home cook. This dish promises to deliver juicy, spice-infused chicken with minimal fuss. Ideal for a quick weeknight dinner or a special weekend feast, this recipe is delicious and visually stunning, making it a surefire hit for family meals and social gatherings. Join me as we explore how to bring the essence of Indian flavors to your kitchen table effortlessly.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hearty Vegetarian Chili: A Cozy and Flavorful Meal</title>
      <link>https://regblog.github.io/food/vegitarian-chili/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 23:35:38 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://regblog.github.io/food/vegitarian-chili/</guid>
      <description>&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Welcome to my kitchen, where we&amp;rsquo;re cooking a batch of heartwarming Vegetarian Chili today. This recipe is perfect for a cozy dinner full of flavor and nourishing ingredients. Let&amp;rsquo;s get started!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ingredients:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Two tablespoons extra-virgin olive oil&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;One medium red onion, chopped&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;One large red bell pepper, chopped&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Two medium carrots, chopped&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Two ribs of celery, chopped&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;¼ teaspoon of salt&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Four cloves garlic, pressed or minced&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Two tablespoons of chili powder&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Two teaspoons of ground cumin&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;1 ½ teaspoons smoked paprika&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;One teaspoon dried oregano&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;One large can (28 ounces) or two small cans (15 ounces each) of diced tomatoes with their juices&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Two cans (15 ounces each) of black beans, rinsed and drained&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;One can (15 ounces) pinto beans, rinsed and drained&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Two cups vegetable broth or water&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;One bay leaf&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;1 to 2 teaspoons of sherry vinegar, red wine vinegar, or lime juice to taste&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fresh cilantro, chopped, for serving&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Instructions:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
