<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Food on REG Blog</title>
    <link>https://reg-blog.com/categories/food/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Food on REG Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 23:42:10 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://reg-blog.com/categories/food/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Festive Cranberry Pecan Goat Cheese Log: A Holiday Appetizer Delight</title>
      <link>https://reg-blog.com/pecan-cranberry-goat-cheese-log/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 23:42:10 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://reg-blog.com/pecan-cranberry-goat-cheese-log/</guid>
      <description>The holiday season is a time for warmth, cheer, and, most importantly, delicious food! If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for an easy yet elegant appetizer to grace your Christmas or New Year&amp;rsquo;s table, look no further than this Cranberry Pecan Goat Cheese Log. Infused with the rich flavors of mature cheddar, fresh herbs, and sweet cranberries, this dish is a delightful blend of textures and tastes to impress your guests.&#xA;Ingredients ½ cup dried cranberries 1 teaspoon butter (salted) ½ cup finely chopped pecans ¼ teaspoon kosher salt 8 oz goat cheese, softened 3 oz Mature/Sharp Cheddar Cheese, grated 2 tablespoons fresh parsley, finely chopped 2 teaspoons fresh rosemary, finely chopped Honey for drizzling Instructions Preparing the Cranberries Boil Water: In a microwave-safe bowl or on the stovetop, bring half a cup of water to a rolling boil.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Easy Homemade Grilled Tandoori Chicken Recipe - Flavorful &amp; Quick!</title>
      <link>https://reg-blog.com/tandoori-chicken/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 23:44:07 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://reg-blog.com/tandoori-chicken/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to a culinary adventure where simplicity meets extraordinary flavor! Today&amp;rsquo;s blog post reveals an incredibly easy-to-follow Grilled Tandoori Chicken recipe perfect for any home cook. This dish promises to deliver juicy, spice-infused chicken with minimal fuss. Ideal for a quick weeknight dinner or a special weekend feast, this recipe is delicious and visually stunning, making it a surefire hit for family meals and social gatherings. Join me as we explore how to bring the essence of Indian flavors to your kitchen table effortlessly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hearty Vegetarian Chili: A Cozy and Flavorful Meal</title>
      <link>https://reg-blog.com/vegitarian-chili/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 23:35:38 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://reg-blog.com/vegitarian-chili/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my kitchen, where we&amp;rsquo;re cooking a batch of heartwarming Vegetarian Chili today. This recipe is perfect for a cozy dinner full of flavor and nourishing ingredients. Let&amp;rsquo;s get started!&#xA;Ingredients:&#xA;Two tablespoons extra-virgin olive oil One medium red onion, chopped One large red bell pepper, chopped Two medium carrots, chopped Two ribs of celery, chopped ¼ teaspoon of salt Four cloves garlic, pressed or minced Two tablespoons of chili powder Two teaspoons of ground cumin 1 ½ teaspoons smoked paprika One teaspoon dried oregano One large can (28 ounces) or two small cans (15 ounces each) of diced tomatoes with their juices Two cans (15 ounces each) of black beans, rinsed and drained One can (15 ounces) pinto beans, rinsed and drained Two cups vegetable broth or water One bay leaf 1 to 2 teaspoons of sherry vinegar, red wine vinegar, or lime juice to taste Fresh cilantro, chopped, for serving Instructions:</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
