<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lives on REG Blog</title>
    <link>https://regblog.github.io/life/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Lives on REG Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 22:13:40 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://regblog.github.io/life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Present Unfolded: My Journey Through Mindful Practices</title>
      <link>https://regblog.github.io/life/the-present-unfolded-my-journey-through-mindful-practices/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 22:13:40 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://regblog.github.io/life/the-present-unfolded-my-journey-through-mindful-practices/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Happy Mindful Monday, everyone! Continuing the spirit of reflection from our Serenity Sunday, today focuses on the art of living in the present. This concept, though simple in theory, can be transformative in practice. Learning to center my attention on the here and now has been key in managing stress and anxiety, leading to a more peaceful daily life.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-present-a-gateway-to-peace&#34;&gt;The Present: A Gateway to Peace&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Harnessing the Power of Now&lt;/strong&gt;: Often, we find ourselves entangled in the web of past memories or future worries. However, the present moment holds a unique power to bring us peace and clarity. By anchoring our thoughts and actions in the present, we allow ourselves to engage fully with life as it unfolds, moment by moment.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Embracing the Now: a Serenity Sunday Reflection</title>
      <link>https://regblog.github.io/life/embracing-the-now-a-serenity-sunday-reflection/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 08:00:12 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://regblog.github.io/life/embracing-the-now-a-serenity-sunday-reflection/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to Serenity Sunday, a day dedicated to slowing down, reflecting, and finding peace in the present moment. Today, I want to share two quotes I wrote this past week. These quotes complement each other beautifully and encapsulate the essence of living mindfully and purposefully.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-quotes&#34;&gt;The Quotes&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Power of Silence and Intention&lt;/strong&gt;&#xA;&amp;ldquo;Not silent from uncertainty but from intention, I anchor myself in the present, letting go of past tides and future storms, cherishing life with love and kindness in its purest form.&amp;rdquo; - Gerjekian (12/27/2023)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charting the Course: REG Blog New Years Resolutions for 2024</title>
      <link>https://regblog.github.io/life/new-years-resolutions-for-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 09:37:10 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://regblog.github.io/life/new-years-resolutions-for-2024/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As REG Blog evolves, I&amp;rsquo;m excited to bring a personal touch to my contributions. While I encourage my friends and family to share their voices freely, without constraints, I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to set a theme for each day that will guide my writing journey. This structure is meant for my posts, offering a glimpse into my world and interests. Here&amp;rsquo;s what you can expect:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;reg-blog-daily-themes-for-my-posts&#34;&gt;REG Blog Daily Themes for My Posts&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;mindful-mondays&#34;&gt;Mindful Mondays&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Mindful Mondays are about starting the week with a calm and centered mindset. Here, I&amp;rsquo;ll delve into various aspects of mental and emotional well-being. From guided meditation practices to discussions on balancing work and life, Mindful Mondays aims to provide practical advice and thoughtful insights. I&amp;rsquo;ll share personal stories of navigating stress and achieving mindfulness and expert advice and tools to help you cultivate a more balanced and fulfilling life.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Top 10 Favorite Places in Washington State: A Summer with AWS</title>
      <link>https://regblog.github.io/life/washington-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 09:19:42 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://regblog.github.io/life/washington-experience/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This past summer, I embarked on an incredible journey with Amazon Web Services (AWS) in Seattle, which led me to discover some of Washington State&amp;rsquo;s most beautiful places. From serene trails and bustling urban squares to breathtaking mountain views, I&amp;rsquo;ve compiled a list of my top 10 favorite spots that capture the essence of the Pacific Northwest. Join me as I recount the adventures and scenery that made my summer in Seattle an unforgettable experience.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
